Anh Tien Nguyen

CONTACT Information Homepage: anhtienng.github.io Email: ngtienanh@korea.ac.kr

RESEARCH INTERESTS My research interest is deep learning in medical image analysis, especially computational histopathology. My current research focuses on whole slide image analysis, such as cancer sub-typing, metastasis detection, and survival prediction.

EDUCATION

Korea University, South Korea

03/2023 - Present

M.S., Computer Engineering

- GPA: 4.38/4.5
- Supervised by Prof. Jin Tae Kwak
- Research area: computational pathology

Ho Chi Minh City University of Technology, Vietnam

08/2017 - 08/2021

B.E., Computer Engineering

- GPA: 9.26/10 Rank 2
- Graduation classification: Excellent

PUBLICATIONS

• Anh Tien Nguyen, Trinh Thi Le Vuong, and Jin Tae Kwak
Towards a text-based quantitative and explainable histopathology image analysis
MICCAI 2024
Early accept, top 11%

- Anh Tien Nguyen and Jin Tae Kwak CAMP: Continuous and Adaptive Learning Model in Pathology Journal - Under review, 2024
- Anh Tien Nguyen and Jin Tae Kwak GPC: Generative and General Pathology Image Classifier MICCAI-MedAGI 2023
 Best Paper Honorable Mention Award

EXPERIENCES

Cloud Ace, Vietnam

10/2021 - 02/2023

Machine learning engineer

- Designed and deployed machine learning solutions on Google Cloud Platform.
- Taught machine learning courses on Google Cloud Platform.

Olli Technology, Vietnam

06/2020 - 09/2020

Machine learning researcher

- Researched and built a Text-to-Speech model to generate Vietnamese natural voice with fast inference speed.
- Deployed a mobile version of machine learning models running on low-spec smartphones.

Google Developer Student Club, Vietnam

11/2019 - 09/2020

Machine learning organizer

• Presented and organized machine learning workshops for university students.

AWARDS

BK21FOUR KU-GAG Scholarship

03/2024

Achieved a scholarship for excellent research projects and publications.

Korea University scholarship

03/2023 - 06/2024

Achieved a Natural Science and Engineering scholarship for excellent research projects and publications.

Honda Award 03/2021

Achieved top 100 nationwide scholarship for Science and Technology students based on merit and research.

HCMC University of Technology scholarship

08/2017 - 08/2021

Achieved scholarships for outstanding students who ranked 5% in a class.

FPT Digital Race

10/2020

Ranked 3^{rd} by designing and deploying an autonomous vehicle control system.

CERTIFICATIONS

Google Cloud Authorized Trainer

03/2022

Authorized to teach the track of data and machine learning.

Coursera Deep Learning Specialization

03/2020

Finished a foundation course on deep learning.

SKILLS

Programming: Python, PyTorch

English: IELTS 7.5

References

• Assoc Prof. Jin Tae Kwak

School of Electrical Engineering, Korea University

Email: jkwak@korea.ac.kr

• Assoc Prof. Tho Thanh Quan

Acting Dean, Faculty of Computer Science and Engineering, HCMC University of

Technology

Email: qttho@hcmut.edu.vn

• Assoc Prof. Thinh Ngoc Tran

Vice Dean, Faculty of Computer Science and Engineering, HCMC University of

Technology

Email: tnthinh@hcmut.edu.vn